Kavish Hukmani

(650) 683-5325 ♦ kshukmani@ucdavis.edu ♦ San Francisco, CA ♦ linkedin.com/in/kavish-hukmani github.com/DoubleGremlin181 ♦ kavishhukmani.me

PROFILE

Master of Science in Business Analytics student at UC Davis with a strong background in Computer Engineering and Big Data.

Specialties: Machine Learning, Exploratory Data Analysis, Computer Vision, Linear Optimization

Technologies: Python, SQL, R, Tableau, Gurobi, Advanced Excel, GCP

Certifications: Coursera courses under the Big Data Specialization by UC San Diego and Deep Learning

Specialization by DeepLearning.AI

EDUCATION

University of California, Davis

San Francisco, CA

Master of Science, Business Analytics

Expected Jun. 2021

Highlighted Coursework: Data Management, Advanced Statistics, Big Data, Cloud Computing, Machine Learning

Manipal Institute of Technology

Manipal, IND

Bachelor of Technology, Major in Computer and Communication Engineering, Minor in Big Data

Aug. 2020

Highlighted Coursework: Data Mining and Predictive Analysis, Computer Vision, Pattern Recognition

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Impact AnalyticsBengaluru, IndiaData ScientistAug. 2020 – Jun. 2021Data ScientistAug. 2020 – Mag. 2020

Data Science Intern Jan. 2020 – Mar. 2020

- Built Linear Programming models in Gurobi, enabling fashion brands such as Tommy Hilfiger, Puma, and Calvin Klein to maximize margins by optimizing promotions and allocation. Received a Spot Award from Impact Analytics for my contributions.
- Trained the preprocessing level of a multilevel CNN classifier which identified SKUs on a store shelf.
- Created a tool for a Fortune 200 supermarket chain to optimize coupon creation and provide members personalized recommendations.

Onward Technologies Chennai, India

Software Intern

Jun. 2019 – Jul. 2019

 Implemented feature detection for a part matching tool to recognize the required components from a blueprint.

Daimler Financial Services India

Pune, India

Summer Intern

May 2018 – Jul. 2018

• Designed a chatbot using DialogFlow for the Mercedes-Benz Finance India social media pages

Additional Qualifications

Projects: Solving Twisty Puzzles using Reinforcement Learning, Twisty Puzzles OpenAI Gym Python Library, Sentiment Analyzer Discord Bot, Contributor to D2ACQ – an open-source online audio quiz game

Awards: MSBA Fellowship at UC Davis, Distinction in Communication Skills - Grade 5 by Trinity College London **Leadership:** Head of Outstation Management and Core Committee Member at TechTatva'18 and Revels'19